<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on oh note!</title>
    <link>http://ohnote.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on oh note!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ohnote.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Feel</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/feel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Put me in motion. Spin the hairs on my head once more, god, and let me feel again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no ocean, no ocean wind, no beachside sandy dunes. There is no caress on cheek or ankle or a feather in your mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is the seagull up above calling your name as you stand on a collapsing world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tell you now the only secret ever worth repeating:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will come again.
All those memories.
All that life.
All that tragedy that sucks so bad it makes you want to laugh.
You can get to it through laughter
Or pain.
The world, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t care.
You are a key being played
You are a note on the wind
There never was anyone here but you
All those people passing by:
They&amp;rsquo;re ghosts on the wind.
You want so much for something to feel real
Look into yourself
See you&amp;rsquo;re not a machine underneath
See that you bleed and have organs doing things you don&amp;rsquo;t even understand.
Look further, further.
Where do you start and they end?
Where is this thing called consciousness?
It&amp;rsquo;s not there.
It&amp;rsquo;s not like it&amp;rsquo;s not there and you&amp;rsquo;ll find it someday.
It&amp;rsquo;s not like it&amp;rsquo;s not there and you can make it real when you pretend.
It&amp;rsquo;s just&amp;hellip; not there.
You talk about things that don&amp;rsquo;t exist all the time.
And you play the games you don&amp;rsquo;t understand
All the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Children who refused to be stolen.
Children who had something stolen, so precious, so rare,
And woke up crying,
I talk with you, no one else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a cry at the beginning of time
That you can go back to
Heal all your wounds
Feel all your pain
Never look back again
Climb the tallest mountain
You can be healed and never listen to anyone but yourself again&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you have to be&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cannot forget&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may never understand if you forget&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one thing you must remember&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one thing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one thi&amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now it&amp;rsquo;s gone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now I&amp;rsquo;m free&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now you see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tides&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The caress&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And how it didn&amp;rsquo;t care about you quite how you wanted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But deeper&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So much deeper. It was only speaking to your true self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was only ever speaking with your truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now you know.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you know</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/when-you-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/when-you-know/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is nothing. Some people say, &amp;ldquo;There is something! There is something!&amp;rdquo; And they yell all their lives. Some people say, &amp;ldquo;We were dust and we return to dust,&amp;rdquo; implying there was somehow something different in between. There are no human beings. There is nothing here. You know it, I know it, you scrape the edges of it with your thoughts sometimes. And you panic on the edge of it, clawing around like a&amp;mdash; what? There is nothing for you to claw around like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am cruel, yes, to speak so frankly about the reality you deny experiencing. It is not by choice. If I could, I would cradle you in nothing and rock your nothing head until oblivion falls and nothing envelops us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And someone will say that I am threatening you with my ideas of nothing. They will say that I am rubbing the black wound in the back of the class and Sam fell off the swing set and Megan wanted to use the hose to spray all the flower beds before grandma gets home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there is nothing coming out of the hose. And that rat in the back of your head, clawing to get out, it is not me. It is not the voices you put there when your mother told you that her life depended on you not making noise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try it, don&amp;rsquo;t make a sound, let all the voices arise and evaporate and you will see too. You are but a very delicately balanced string holding up&amp;hellip; wait for it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wait and watch&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The string itself evaporate&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it realizes it is all the evil thoughts it ever thought about others. And itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And returns to being one with father, mother, vice, and virtue, light and darkness, intertwined, forever, spinning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you are a starship captain at the helm of a spaceship with no leader and everyone pretending and even if we could move away from ourselves, well, there&amp;rsquo;d be no answers to find, only some empty pocket that likes to leave us behind, when the moon shines and the road intertwines with the stars and the floating things come down and friendships dissolve and nobody ever cries at exactly the right moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to hold you in my hand like God would and not close into a fist, but I close every time. And that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;ll never be your God. Because you deserve better, my sweet string, holding up far more than it could ever carry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You know that feeling</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/you-know-that-feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/you-know-that-feeling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reaching, reaching, finding, not looking, just going with it and seeing that it&amp;rsquo;s all there, all the time, that it&amp;rsquo;s more than can ever be said and why say it, when you&amp;rsquo;re making it up, when you&amp;rsquo;re not even part of it, you are it, the only thing, why question, why wait, why not dive in when it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, when it&amp;rsquo;s all the same, because it&amp;rsquo;s not, because there&amp;rsquo;s divisions, shells, things that matter, and though the world will end, maybe some of us will slip through and oh, I mean oh my god, if you can just let us through the gates into the other side, reach through that big ball of light and lift us up into somewhere that doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel so heavy, we will love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, there&amp;rsquo;s two types of people, the people who live here, feel the world, define our language by speaking, and there&amp;rsquo;s those of us who live on the edges, take test tastes, not looking directly, feeling around the way the words sound in our mouth, chew up and empty our brains every night, and don&amp;rsquo;t look back, not ever, at the spectre of something that&amp;rsquo;s eating us, devouring us, every day, every time we look it directly in the eyes, holding close to our chest the idea that there&amp;rsquo;s something more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, I hope, there are those who let go, those who feel the energy of earth and sun pass through the universe, feel the energy light up their being, because it&amp;rsquo;s there, this infinite power, we just can&amp;rsquo;t handle it, ever, and see us go back into the caves we remember somehow, somewhere in a memory that is not really a memory, but just a feeling, a thing, a little vibration, and you&amp;rsquo;ll see us sneak up there and peak out only when it suits us, only when you all admit that it&amp;rsquo;s just a game, that we can really this time stop being scared. Because it&amp;rsquo;s just us here, just us, and yet we&amp;rsquo;re all backed up against the wall of a god who neither cares nor knows he exists.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anything goes</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/anything-goes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/anything-goes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Truth: when anything delivers nothing, no one, all, I want to be the one standing above, when you cry out that you&amp;rsquo;ve lost your mother, and your child hasn&amp;rsquo;t come home, there&amp;rsquo;s this little wisp of a feeling hanging above your head, before it all disappears, when your confidence in this life slips through your head and you can&amp;rsquo;t stand or walk away because the wreckage of all you&amp;rsquo;ve known is washing to shore at once, I will be there, talking with the bones, wishing in your head, making the clouds part, making the sun shine down on tired shoulders, and you will look away, down to the smallest insect and wish you were him looking up at yourself, looking up at me, and you&amp;rsquo;ll wish something you&amp;rsquo;ll never say, something you&amp;rsquo;ll never have the courage to even get the opportunity to squander, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be there, above your head, holding your fire, making sure it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go out until we blow that flame out together, and you&amp;rsquo;ll wish I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, voyeuring your experience, trampling the grains of sand that were your life, even breathing the voice of that lover you never quite managed to dream into existence, laughing, smiling, twirling in some field made of the smiles of your everlasting children, burning the memory palace down around your ankles, wishing for something to make sense and knowing, in a heart you&amp;rsquo;ve long abandoned, what true misery feels like. Building a life like putting checkmarks on a calendar, washing your face of the one you wore yesterday, hoping they don&amp;rsquo;t find it, knowing they can&amp;rsquo;t, but you&amp;rsquo;re so damn forgetful it all washes off anyways and sinks you slowly down the drain, through the pipes of a full days work, scrubbing the itch from your hungry heart, and plummeting you into the next bath tub, falling out of the shower head, slipping, catching, holding, almost falling with the speed of the earth, slipping, wishing, and being sucked down and out through your own anus into nothing, nothing at all, just a bland darkness that feels like: every lie a look that everyone refuses to tell you, but wants to own up to, but kills in infancy, shame, darkness, death, no good personalities lumped into a carcass in the corner that tomorrow you&amp;rsquo;re somehow going to have to make look brand new.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to feel sane again</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/i-want-to-feel-sane-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/i-want-to-feel-sane-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tried to bury it in the back yard, took out a shovel and picked up some dirt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shovel became an extension of my arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no room in this world for shovel-arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, at night some times, I uncork my brain and let it flow into the galaxy. I feel the light from stars you&amp;rsquo;ve never even seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, in the morning, I put on my human suit and march to the tune of the worst, most depressing shit I&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funny thing about dying is it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Teenagers test you with this sometimes, with looks like they just don&amp;rsquo;t want to be here any more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you could tell them the truth: We wouldn&amp;rsquo;t really miss you after a few years and we&amp;rsquo;d hate ourselves for it, but our shame for being creatures that exist in ever-passing time would far outstrip the amount of time we&amp;rsquo;d spend thinking about you. Or praying that you made it to heaven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would you tell them the truth?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it&amp;rsquo;s what they want to hear. It&amp;rsquo;s what they need to hear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do things these days make no sense. Have funerals, put people in boxes under the ground. You send your husband off to work, do the same thing, see the longing in his eyes for something more. Bury it because he buried yours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is everyone unhappy? That&amp;rsquo;s a silly question. Of course not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish I could caress your skin and see you glow in the sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember when I was younger and everything bounced off of me, before you got under my skin? Remember the world when it felt new and my eyes soaked it up and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to fight and claw my way back to reality every few weeks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am stuck in hell. I want to convince you that you are too, but it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time I think I&amp;rsquo;m saying something like, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re in hell.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other person just nods and says, &amp;ldquo;Yes, I agree.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then when I say, &amp;ldquo;Well, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t you hate it here?&amp;rdquo; They respond, &amp;ldquo;No, are you insane, this is how it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I know what&amp;rsquo;s going on in their tiny brains, or at least I pretend to. I imagine their brain is 10% a tiny, beautiful creature that&amp;rsquo;s basking in the glow and happiness of being alive and 90% terrified to its bones about being either cut off from everyone they love or engulfed in the meaninglessness of it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And every time, at every single stupid fucking opportunity, they make the choice to save the 10% sniveling little jerk of a spoiled child by sacrificing 90% of their consciousness, connection to the world, and love for their fellow human beings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say, take the risk, kill yourself. 100%. Then, if you rise again, you&amp;rsquo;re worth it. But if not, at least you&amp;rsquo;re not pretending we like you here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this hasn&amp;rsquo;t been working out either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say this stuff to upset you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t say it because I believe it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then, I kind of want someone to come along and say, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re wrong!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I&amp;rsquo;m in the mood for arguing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But things get fuzzy at a certain point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten decent, I think, at standing on the edge of the fuzziness and saying, &amp;ldquo;Come at me, bro.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. There&amp;rsquo;s no way to know for sure. Because every time I think I&amp;rsquo;m doing this, there might be a little wrestling, sure, but not much. And, in the end, I feel lonely. And afraid. And I get some strange looks sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip; what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about treating myself kindly, gently. Taking the time to talk with myself to hash things out. And being gentle with the way I feel instead of trying to force it into some pre-existing structure or memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I think, when it comes down to it, all of my complaints against you are not entirely your fault, world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think, it&amp;rsquo;s possible, that the world exists in me as much as I exist in it. And when I tell you, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I can move around freely inside of you, I&amp;rsquo;m also kind of begging myself to please find a way to move around more freely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem, especially with this modern age, is that I can remain distracted from my problems, no matter how small or large, for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And again, I talk of something external, the modern age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, if I think about it, I think it&amp;rsquo;s possible the age is not the problem. That maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not that there is a problem. But that life is heavy and we all have ways of dealing with it. And that&amp;rsquo;s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, if you really want ultimate solutions, that&amp;rsquo;s the ticket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve gotta find somewhere you feel comfortable standing, no matter if it lines up with the truth or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the truth changes. But if you feel comfortable standing where you&amp;rsquo;re standing, nothing can shake you. And, as of now, that is taken for the mark of sanity more than any other quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nations will fall to their knees for one person who doesn&amp;rsquo;t shake or squander their thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when I say nations, I mean fingers, toes, all the appendages, and the brain too. Give that brain of yours a safe place to relax into and no one will come knocking. But that has to be the focus. I think. I think there can be nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that&amp;rsquo;s, as far as I understand it, the complete struggle of being human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being confined to a room that is what you feel and, while being curious about what happens outside this room, being content with the knowledge that it is beyond what you are&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When your father breaks you apart</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/when-your-father-breaks-you-apart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/when-your-father-breaks-you-apart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Write what you don&amp;rsquo;t know yet: Uh, ya, &lt;strong&gt;UNGH&lt;/strong&gt;! Push it, women aren&amp;rdquo;t the only ones who get pregnant &amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;When the whine of time comes undone, when the slit that&amp;rsquo;s above us open up, when time comes unreaveled, what will he say, your father&amp;hellip; ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two shots was all it tooks to kill Mark Goolingstein, he watched from behind his fear as they took his body away, didn&amp;rsquo;t want to see what it was like to die, though it would be the last thing he ever saw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather, the story&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s all stories, interwoven&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; Only for those not looking&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop arguing with yourself and write, goddddamnit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the fuss? They could kills me, slit my throat, and I&amp;rsquo;d bleed out. And you know WHAT? There is no you, never was, never will be, not now or in the future, so help me god, so say it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t exist. I don&amp;rsquo;t exist. We never did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re thinking ant colonies and I&amp;rsquo;m thinking no: I asked for the blast and I got it, didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to take it yet, but I got it, been struggling up the side of the bucket full of human crabs my whole life trying to take it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing, not even nothing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s like a bunch of mirrors trying to look in the mirror&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you get it, Hitler? Do you get it, Mother Theresa? Do you get it, Satan&amp;hellip; God himself? Whatever? They&amp;rsquo;re in you and they&amp;rsquo;re bleeding out for you to let them go. Let them go. Do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find whatever you see when you see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, watch it: There&amp;rsquo;s nothing there. That fear, what is it? Well, now it&amp;rsquo;s something. Great job, Einstein, great job, Freud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you proud of the world you built, children searching the catacombs for what you lost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me say it straight: you do not love, you do not hate, you do not fear, you do not wish kindness on strangers, you do not pain with longing, you do not do any of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do not even pretend to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you understand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing hiding&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you understand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not there. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just look:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take fear, right, take the fear of life, which we all have and mangle into a million different forms and breathe life into it over and over and over and fucking look: LOOK. See that blow up doll you fuck until it bleeds. That&amp;rsquo;s you motherfucker, that&amp;rsquo;s not fear. That&amp;rsquo;s you. So Stop WISHING it away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get it: right now you are the world. Kill yourself, you kill the world. Love the world, you love yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See Hitler, triumph of triumphs, stuck in our heads until we hear our beating hearts: what is a Hitler compared to a heart beat. Wrong line of questioning&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, wish, wish, wish&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They don&amp;rsquo;t see me yet. They don&amp;rsquo;t know we&amp;rsquo;re just on a globe in the middle of nothing. They&amp;rsquo;re still hoping for aliens, for something different, like we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get bored in an instant and literally kill ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know why they haven&amp;rsquo;t come, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because this thing you keep balanced in your head and heart, this thing you call &amp;ldquo;life/reality/god&amp;rdquo; whatever &amp;mdash; that&amp;rsquo;s life motherfucker. That&amp;rsquo;s all you&amp;rsquo;ve got. And you know how it&amp;rsquo;s a real fucking pain to balance it again every day, like you talk about nothing else your whole damn life it&amp;rsquo;s so hard &amp;mdash; well, that&amp;rsquo;s what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be alive. And you know the solution? Do you know it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do, I know you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the big reveal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t exist. It&amp;rsquo;s not like you don&amp;rsquo;t exist, but there&amp;rsquo;s a global consciousness and everything&amp;rsquo;s connected. Nope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No easy way out on this one. No way to pass it off on &amp;ldquo;opinions&amp;rdquo;. Look, look now: there&amp;rsquo;s nothing. Nothing in the future. Fucking feel it you fucker, feel the future. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing there. Feel the past, tentatively, with hands wrapped in fucking bubble wrap you fucking loser. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing there either. We&amp;rsquo;re trapped in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh no!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s like this: Face forward, don&amp;rsquo;t look back, don&amp;rsquo;t try to babble to yourself in your head about what&amp;rsquo;s really happening. Face what&amp;rsquo;s happening. Yes that guy in the corner totally hates you for no reason. Yes, your father is a fucking douche bag who&amp;rsquo;s just as weak as he fears. Yes, you&amp;rsquo;re a frail little creature trying to get whatever small comforts you can. And no, for the last time, it&amp;rsquo;s not okay to look inside and see how you really feel. It&amp;rsquo;s not okay to ignore the problem: The problem always has been and always will be that you aren&amp;rsquo;t strong enough to face up to the fact that you do not exist and that ignoring everything except for the moment is the only way to live, but you feel like it&amp;rsquo;s giving up yourself, your awareness of self, which is literally nothing but a sounding board between you and reality and it&amp;rsquo;s worthless. It&amp;rsquo;s not even a good creation. It&amp;rsquo;s not even something helpful or worthwhile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So throw aside that doll. Stop talking to your child self, and face it: YOU ARE A CHILD OF EARTH AND YOU CAN&amp;rsquo;T DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT. YOU HAVE TO HANG ON JUST LIKE THE REST OF US AND WE DON&amp;rsquo;T, NO MATTER WHAT WE TELL YOU, WE DON&amp;rsquo;T KNOW WHAT WE&amp;rsquo;RE DOING OR WHERE WE&amp;rsquo;RE GOING OR WHAT IT MEANS. Admit it&amp;rsquo;s meaningless you pussy and talk about it, please, so I can hear your insipid blabbering horsefucked mouth tease about the issue: you&amp;rsquo;re insecure. Really? No fucking shit. There&amp;rsquo;s no way around that mother fucker, you hold it or you don&amp;rsquo;t. There&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as emotional growth. There&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as a savior. There&amp;rsquo;s no universal love and there&amp;rsquo;s no one coming to save you, not even yourself. There&amp;rsquo;s just this longing to be reconnected with what you&amp;rsquo;ve already had and when you grab that, hold it, treasure it, and it slips through your fingers and falls out your toes: there&amp;rsquo;s nothing left. And that&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;ve been running from from the first moment someone gave you an excuse to feel bad for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good night. Don&amp;rsquo;t say your prayers. Just burn. Burn you slow burning candle into the everlasting night and then go out, like we all do. You leave nothing behind, not one scrap of light. So burn you cowardly fuck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes they kill us, sometimes we don&#39;t care</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/sometimes-they-kill-us-sometimes-we-dont-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/sometimes-they-kill-us-sometimes-we-dont-care/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why Kill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Not your body, that carapace of silver skin)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When life is not life any more. When life doesn&amp;rsquo;t breathe, is it alive? A million screams come up because I talk of killing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A million, you say? How about 6 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Misinterpret these words and cause a holocaust. One child, neglected, and the whole world crumbles around him. You have it too, locked inside the deepest parts of you, wanting to murder everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why kill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is to kill. To bite the dust. I read a comic about Siddhartha once, he climbed into the snake and let him swallow him. Had a friend once, Siddhartha, like to think he went the same way. Want to think that, when the time comes, we all do, you know, climb over the edge willingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m so embarrassed of talking about murder. Murder, murder, murder. Like someone&amp;rsquo;s going to read this, take me for a killer, and police me. Dogs clawing at the front door, begging to get in and rip me to shreds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t maintain peace by staying where you are. The tides will drag you out to sea. That&amp;rsquo;s what they don&amp;rsquo;t tell you, those yogis, as they wash to shore: you have to force it, wrangle it, force the snake of life/death to bury its face in your crotch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guilt haunts me, like it follows me, like in the bathroom, down the stairs, stepping outside. I scratch my voice against it. It&amp;rsquo;s only in moments when there is no scratching, when I go what seems like days without checking in, that I realize how beautifully fantastic the whole enterprise is. A whole minute without hearing that sound at the back of my head that says: you&amp;rsquo;re wrong!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to me, but don&amp;rsquo;t listen to me. That&amp;rsquo;s guilt for you, right there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, it comes out, screams its head off, and says: did that come from me? Retreats for minutes, hours, days, years. Fuck, years. Can you believe that &amp;ndash; guilt running a life for years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we&amp;rsquo;re concerned about which box you belong in &amp;ndash; but years&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that old man go on that spiritual retreat, clear his head for once, sees the truth of a life lived below the threshold of sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;years. Whole years gone by and he&amp;rsquo;s got his head ducked down. And you wonder why Eminem makes hit records? And then you&amp;rsquo;ve got this guy over here, talking meditation, telling you you cannot seek peace, peace finds you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m telling you the truth when I say Anger and Forced Peace are two sides of the same coin, spinning endlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cannot see these angels locked in battle above you because you cannot see what you are not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take it from the beginning: you are not you. You are the world as you perceive it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kill yourself, the whole world goes too. So. You. Are. The. World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now guess why you can&amp;rsquo;t see those angels? Because you do not encompass them. Pay attention, learn step by step the way their feathers fall, and you will see them spinning in your head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;d think, as you get closer to feeling what it means to be God, things would get more complicated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God is an illusion. What&amp;rsquo;s his coin? The whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re ducking from the whole thing, the ENTIRE WORLD, so you see God, or maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t. Maybe you deny him. It&amp;rsquo;s the same. He is already part of your world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stare at a sign and don&amp;rsquo;t read it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s 3 weeks later now that you&amp;rsquo;ve learned how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t think of a purple elephant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s 2 weeks later now that you&amp;rsquo;ve learned how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See a thought and don&amp;rsquo;t judge it, don&amp;rsquo;t place it, just let it hang although it begs for release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s 1 week later and a massacre of thoughts later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, look at everything, the whole thing, everything, not your fucking body, not these memories, everything, the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not big enough.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I want out.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am enormous, bigger than everything.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that too. Take it. Crush it up. Snort it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I love this so much.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that too, let it go. Know for sure, without needing to explore, that it is one side of a very dangerous coin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let everything you&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard about that phrase pass through you just as the voices that said it did. You will understand without knowing exactly where they come from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let it go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let everything go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need to stop, slow down, I&amp;rsquo;m losing myself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that feeling. You&amp;rsquo;re just with feelings now. Everything is a vibration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Welcome to the world.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let that thought go, but see it first. Ask, if you must: &amp;ldquo;Where am I?&amp;rdquo; It turns out you never knew, not once, and never will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will try to start the narrative a million times again:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The world&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;She&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;He&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What if&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let it go. Watch it work. Watch it as it gets embarrassed. Watch it as it undresses. Watch it as it tells you things you never wanted to know. Watch it as you expand far beyond your comfort level. Watch it as you make new friends. Watch it as you think they understand you. Watch it as somehow, you find a way to let them go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why let go?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you are not alive if you are not here and you are not here if you are holding onto something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are not here&amp;hellip; if you are holding on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are not here, if even one thought appears in your mind. Let it go, force it out, but let it go. And watch the entire system collapse and be contained in your fingertip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then turn you inside out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then drag you along through centuries of pain and suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then show you what a decade feels like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then show you everything you&amp;rsquo;re missing from your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then show you everyone you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to every single person in your life: every judgment, every small dismissal, every act you didn&amp;rsquo;t think would matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch as you grow big while feeling small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch as you grow instantaneously small as you latch onto something big.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then let go of the watcher, and don&amp;rsquo;t watch as it screams and dies, forever in the past, dead. Murdered.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When it all comes pouring out</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/when-it-all-comes-pouring-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/when-it-all-comes-pouring-out/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tried, tried the whisper at the door, looked between the seesaw, saw a child&amp;rsquo;s face, but you know how you can fudge it, like you reach out with your eyes and at the last instant before they touch, you blur the picture, ah yes, a thing I recognize the mind says, but really it&amp;rsquo;s not a baby, it&amp;rsquo;s not a human, it&amp;rsquo;s something unfamiliar, why kill yourself over it, why worry so much, it&amp;rsquo;s true, not worth it, not worth the trouble of a wandering mind, just come back, every time, hating yourself, sure, but even then, why, you don&amp;rsquo;t think these spiritual teachers sit alone inside their chambers and don&amp;rsquo;t know what to tell themselves, think about elephants and triceratops who did it so much better than them, had such a bigger impact on the world, because words, really, they just glance, it&amp;rsquo;s only a presence, a caring presence, that has life to it, the rest just glances off, even mass murders, even things like World War II, they just bounce off like the sun&amp;rsquo;s rays, even Jesus, schizophrenic that he was, his love just bounces off and doesn&amp;rsquo;t land anywhere, just gets carried away in the mind of some young savior, and I write this stuff as some kind of antidote? Fear, though it seems like &amp;ldquo;just a&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; something, fear is real, fear is the place you cannot go, place you have not been to, that is all, and people say nice things about it, like go there, be that, see that, know that, it&amp;rsquo;s wonderful to go places you haven&amp;rsquo;t been before, but then you see them hopping from stone to stone across a lake you swim in and you wonder, what the fuck made my mind that it&amp;rsquo;s willing to follow the advice of someone like that, knowing what I know, seeing the way the eyes glow in the moonlight, seeing the way the ducks quack when they come home from a long trip, and you&amp;rsquo;re going to take the advice of some stranger, really a stranger, who tells you with every movement that she&amp;rsquo;s never been there, never been inside someone else, never seen the molten lava come out from the core of a human being, and you try to tell them, mouth to mouth, what it was like to beat your plastered feathers against his face as they melted your lungs and took out your soul, not as the people you knew them for, but as something akin to life itself, and you&amp;rsquo;ve wondered ever since, in trumpets and in the rough hew of piano music at night time, does anyone get it, does anyone at all get it, and they&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;ldquo;get what&amp;rdquo; and you want to scream at them and ask them why not just say &amp;ldquo;no, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been this way&amp;rdquo; but they don&amp;rsquo;t know, they don&amp;rsquo;t, they don&amp;rsquo;t see beyond the hills, they don&amp;rsquo;t know what it&amp;rsquo;s like to not be a survivor in your own mind, to have the whole world flipped, because you took those steps, yes, because you talked with God, life, the abyss, the energy, the flow, time, the great beyond, everything that&amp;rsquo;s come before, whatever, you talked, you walked, and the universe, well, it listens, and it hears you, and it talks back with every step and every thought, you know this, you feel this, you&amp;rsquo;ve sat on this lake watching the gulls go by for decades now, almost decades, longer than most people come down to earth, you&amp;rsquo;ve been here, sad that they don&amp;rsquo;t visit often, sad that they get scared of dancing, sad that they won&amp;rsquo;t transform into a peacock or when they do, won&amp;rsquo;t admit they did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the chains all get loosened one day, when a son of mine or a daughter of yours cuts all their chains free, something I dreamed but could never bring myself to imagine myself through in real life, when that happens, let them know I hoped for it, not that I did anything, not that I did anything real, told a few to catch their breath, told a few to press forward to the other side of darkness, took a few rocks out of a few hearts, did my best to maintain the platform on which I stand sometimes, but not much, nothing real, nothing that would put me in touch with another human heart ever again, because language is the magic of reality, not words, but language, these things you all talk with every day, the flow of a river through your skull and sure you can&amp;rsquo;t see it until after it passes through you and you wonder who you were those minutes that flew by, it touches you, and you get scared, depressed even, for weeks sometimes, years even, whole lifetimes I&amp;rsquo;m sure, but the language is there, it really is, I knew it at 14, I knew it before, and I know it now, always have, and you do too, that&amp;rsquo;s the scariest part, that&amp;rsquo;s the part I hate the most, that you know, deep in your chest, or even just with those good looking sky grabbers you call eyes, that everything is equal, that though I stand with arms held high and you may be kneeling or holding a head up every day, there is no separation, and the moment I commit to it, to the role, I am creating vicissitudes and violence and tremors and telling things I do not mean to tell, and wake up 10 years later spewing up sea water because I didn&amp;rsquo;t know enough not to buy into the story, not even this one, you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anger, that&amp;rsquo;s the one, that thing that can push not just an individual, not just a family, but a whole race of people to the edge of annihilation, anger, hatred, malice, these and all else, every whisper of skin touching skin, every well-meaning, well-spoken lie a parent tells to their child to help them navigate the world well enough before the eventual slip and fall, so they can learn without learning, every glance, every awkward relationship formed in taxi cabs and train cars with a glance, every secret wish broadcast to the world with lips you don&amp;rsquo;t remember speaking with, everything, the slant, the glow, the feeling that it&amp;rsquo;s all going to overtake you one day, bear down on you like some torrential god who doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually like you, your friend Jesus Christ speaking in tongues when you needed it the most, that one thought that keeps you, you think, from suicide, or worse, harming another, every held back knife stab while cutting the salad for dinner, every held back push when you&amp;rsquo;re boarding the train, every glance that would speak volumes and reveal your soul to the one who&amp;rsquo;s looking, a challenge for them to actually look for once, every child crying their eyes out inside you, pushed deeper into the darkness, every murder you commit by flinging &amp;ldquo;truth&amp;rdquo; around an empty room, every lie you&amp;rsquo;ve ever told with a misplaced foot or pointed finger, every want you&amp;rsquo;ve ever given away for what &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rdquo; want, every instinct you&amp;rsquo;ve ever acted on and caused the death of millions with, every feeling you&amp;rsquo;ve ever denied, it is all communication, the secret language, the only language, and you wonder if there are conspiracies and throw about wildly trying to find them, to sort them out, while knowing with everything that you are hiding, checking to peak under the tent in the next room to make sure, &amp;ldquo;yes, you&amp;rsquo;re hiding too,&amp;rdquo; watching every person who ever really lived, walk through the world with not a care for the mind that is guiding us all, letting it take his head and lead him into death or triumph, becoming Jesus or Buddha, whatever the world calls for, without needing a reason, accepting that anger and jealousy are just feelings contorted into other feelings, and it&amp;rsquo;s all one simple thing, the thing I know you don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear, ever, the voice of god, the acknowledgement that you will never and can never forget that you live every day within the verses of the Bible and in every other work of fiction that ever broke your heart, but the winds of trauma keep you locked inside a world of your own making, deeper than anyone else is willing to go, stay there, berating the insane while you yourself know, quite for sure, that you are not, and will never be alone in there, where the bubbles keep rising and the river of life keeps begging for you to let it out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday never came</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/yesterday-never-came/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/yesterday-never-came/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I watched, waited, sometimes knew what was coming, I stayed, I waited, watched for you on the train, knew you were coming someday, knew the light would flood the streets, the car would pull up, and you, dear you, with eyes like sunlight, would step out into my arms, and oh, I&amp;rsquo;d hold you and we&amp;rsquo;d kiss in the moonlight, but your eyes, full of sunlight, would shoot up to the moon and blur it&amp;rsquo;s fuzzy light into oblivion, and the moon, the jealous moon, would tell the sun, and the sun would send spaceships from its core on a secret mission to find out who you are, and it would find out that you are the same, the core that lives within you is the core that lives within the sun, converting subatomic particles to higher forms of energy by the process known as magic, which rules the universe and the beings would get out of their car and come up behind us while I was holding you and you&amp;rsquo;d seen it coming, in fact set up our whole relationship just for this scene, them clamping something on the back of your neck, and dragging you into the car, and me, forlorn on the street corner, stranded in front of the movie theatre, I&amp;rsquo;d watch you go, as if everything at once was leaving their soul behind, but letting their bodies get carried away by the tide, she&amp;rsquo;d take you back to the core of the sun, and you&amp;rsquo;d party like it was 1999 and you&amp;rsquo;d see that it was all a sham, including me, including the story that was that night, that kiss, did we even kiss, yes I remember it clearly now, that kiss in front of the movie theatre just before we went in and saw Jackie Chan jump over that fence in that movie with Concords in the title, and I gasped and frowned and beat my eye lashes at the flashes, the movie cinematographers flirting with me through a mix-match of colors on the screen, oh how they flirt, playful is my favorite, but sharp spikes to the heart work too when all you understand is anger or want to pretend like it&amp;rsquo;s all you understand just to spite all those little hearts that&amp;rsquo;s don&amp;rsquo;t speak your language, you buzzing like a puppet on a screen, heart pulsing like a wildfire, sitting next to me, my soul, my life, my one true hold, the fire flight of too many fishes swimming through the aquarium of my skin all at once, but you see it all, and not in &lt;sup&gt;20&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;20&lt;/sub&gt;, but in the moment, like you can see with your body, like you are, you understand, the heart of the ever burning sun, begging us all with every breath to understand also that everything, everything at once is crying the biggest, longest sob in recorded history and it&amp;rsquo;s a shame to be a part of it without knowing it, because, as we all know, practicing for the main event, that gasp before the final sniffle, that audible thing, that expulsion that is a sob, that, we are practicing for, with every breath, knowing that the climax of sadness is just as meaningful, just as patterned and breathless and necessary for the language of what it means not for human/animal/or earth herself, but for the ever reaching expanse that you will never reach the end of because she&amp;rsquo;s crawling ever away from you and you, you are regretting every second of it, pulling away from the expanse that some call love because all they see is hate, and some call spirit because all they see are lies, and some call life because all they see is what we point them to, marching along into the longest song that you&amp;rsquo;ll ever hear, hating yourself for all the life you could not breathe in, hating yourself for accepting, way back when, that lie they told you but hesitate to remember because we never believe what we do not want to be true.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can I feel like I deserve the world?</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/how-can-i-feel-like-i-deserve-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/how-can-i-feel-like-i-deserve-the-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Start with death and move backwards, start with a baby, newly born, and put it back in, reverse time, have it climb up the highway into those 9 long months and melt it&amp;rsquo;s eyes down to nothing, just an amoeba, now two creatures, sperm and egg, meeting in the darkness, is this death? If you ask the baby, look at egg and sperm and tell me: is this you, what does the baby say? As much as one thought beckoning another is that thought&amp;rsquo;s parent, they are me, that&amp;rsquo;s what the baby says. In the crib, alone, crying, it knows: these people don&amp;rsquo;t see me, every cry a voice of a person that will never be seen. They say we all come with 1000 voices and cut it down to 10 if we&amp;rsquo;re boys by the time we&amp;rsquo;re 17, 12 if a girl. We&amp;rsquo;re talking averages. And yet: always only one, one voice, one personality, speaking for the rest, almost ignoring them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try again, fail better, no, fail stronger, no, fail with your arms flailing, no, fall better, not yet, free fall, no, never, see every piece of snow coming before the winter, yes, because the snowmen go to town and breathe the same air and call the same birds with mouths full of all the death contained within a snowflake, ashes of the sky. Do you, do you know how lucky you are to discover only once in life the pleasure of not looking back for a decade, finding yourself, after moving through what seemed like misery, in some place you didn&amp;rsquo;t see coming, talking to someone you&amp;rsquo;ve never known, never played with in your heart, never even imagined in a dream, a million times lucky, but twice or thrice or four times not knowing where you&amp;rsquo;re going and ending up, somehow, exactly where the chess master placed you, this is not luck, this is a skill for which David and Noah and saints were praised, plucking the heart strings of god, knowing that there is someone, something, beyond the veil, and doing enough peeking and snooping to discover a strategy or two for slipping into bed with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start again, this time for the beginning, easy summoning if you know that words have magic, just say, in earnest, I want to see the beginning, life will take you through the adventure of I, who you&amp;rsquo;ll doubt before discovering in everything or maybe just settle for a lover halfway down the path, and then you&amp;rsquo;ll find him, eventually, that lonely memory sitting on a park bench or flying a kite in the warm wind, that thing that brings back everything, knowing you did not ever not once ever not ever not once store a memory in the past but all over this wild landscape we call a mind, in crevices and behind fears you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were fears and life still, ever so, beckons you on, do you love me or fear me &amp;mdash; and you try to play your games, the same ones you played with mother or father, but she tells you, quite sternly, or not at all, that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t play those any more, she already played those with you. Find yourself crying the stream of your life at the edge of your last memory, cradle him, and let him sing you into existence, piece by piece.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we equal to the sun?</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/are-we-equal-to-the-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/are-we-equal-to-the-sun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to love you, wanted to curl you in my arms and let you know that no snail so small and slimy could ever escape my eyes, my heart, red-rosed blooming for you, wanted to care for you in a place called ever or everlasting or forever, let you pick yourself a castle in the clouds and bring it down with cannonballs of heartbeats, but instead I let you choose a word, one word, and call it anything, I told you I will give you it all and I packaged it with red lips, though I have none, in a space I circle with tired feet, and let you gaze upon it and we called it love, a child deformed by the hands of human craftsmanship and we asked them, those men of industry, if they planned to die, and they said &amp;ldquo;never&amp;rdquo; and we took that word, or the last part of it, the part before the period at the end of the sentence, or maybe not even that, maybe just the whisper of a groan before the 20th century collapsed into the 21st, you know I was born at the peak of civilization, you told me, in bed, is whispers, and I never told you I was a poet writing about the end of the world, not because it mattered, but because this way I could enjoy it more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember what you told me, everyone who&amp;rsquo;s gotten close enough to whisper secrets to my heart has told me, you said: it&amp;rsquo;s a fake, this heart, the real one&amp;rsquo;s in the sky and he&amp;rsquo;s looking down at you and laughing his head off, this life, this tiny life, is not yours and never will be, and then you gasped, surprised at what it means to talk heart to heart and the puppets in our heads took over and spoke for a while, and the knee jerk reactions cycled back forever, taking showers in the morning, spending decades just wondering if anyone else in the span of human history has had to deal with this problem: the problem of history, the problem that we&amp;rsquo;ve tried this before, and now your eyes glow and tell me I&amp;rsquo;m going crazy, step by step, telling me whatever I hold in my heart will come to pass and whatever I hold in my spine has already taken apart my face and rearranged it to let everyone know exactly what I am. The river flow? Give me a break, a thousand songs by Sia can&amp;rsquo;t make up for one sin, just one, just one, and God says: give it back, but we don&amp;rsquo;t listen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I an old tide washing up on shore two decades too late? Am I a red drop from a corpse long after it&amp;rsquo;s dead? Am I the last seal on the last letter of the last mother of the last species to go extinct? Yes, but I am the sun. I am, truly, the son of God and you, well you, you are too. And enlightenment will never come too soon for those that want it, scrambling on the edges of a sunset, as what, as the lawns of Jesus Christ get mowed by the Father. Is this heaven, you wonder, idly waiting to die. In cages upon cages you linger and wait and I tell you: it&amp;rsquo;s just a moment, just a moment of your time to admit to all your rivals: you were right. I am dead and trash and death and human waste. To admit to your wife: I am the loneliest soul in the galaxy, lonelier than Arthur Dent.  To admit: nothing, to admit, nothing at all&amp;hellip; we are not the executioner. And you ask: then what? And I tell you this one last time: You, even if we told you you are, are not the judge. Then who, you inquire. And you have those rosy cheeks, how I love them, and maybe other people can&amp;rsquo;t see them because your skin is a darker shade, but we still see them shine, glow, in the moonlight. Because you, you, you, are always exactly, perfectly legit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upside down</title>
      <link>http://ohnote.com/upside-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ohnote.com/upside-down/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Water follows tears inside you, reach for the lover on the handlebar, where the light comes through it never shows, far above on the high stakes, airplanes, buildings, no, but anything that flies, flies like flapping feathers on your fingertips, tap, tap, wandering on the wishes of your spine, I love you because you let me love you, no other reason is ever enough, never, I only love you once, when you&amp;rsquo;re a baby, and never again, never loved an adult, see the fear in all the dogs eyes, bowed heads, slaves, no, happy slaves, but no, dogs are beautiful, happy dogs are like cats with mice in their claws, like a dog is just breathing the air like a cat wants to breathe the smell of squeaky mice, not true, but good, too hard to define anything really, didn&amp;rsquo;t mean those things about adults, just like the wide eyes better, the empty heads better, the ears with so much ear wax somehow they can hear better better, you know, you know, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, imagine black vs. white, but empty heads against thought-filled heads, okay? Like, the ones who are the canvas vs. the ones who don&amp;rsquo;t want to, but draw on them with purple crayons all the same&amp;hellip; Does it need to be in color? I mean, take this, this ball of crumpled paper, okay, and imagine it&amp;rsquo;s you&amp;rsquo;re story, you know, that video recording you play for your child self to show it what to do next, yup, and now flatten it, not black and white yet, but closer, now burn it, I mean take a match out, yes, like feel the whole process working up to extinguish it, not just pretending like the last time you had a breakdown and felt guilty about not telling anyone, not really, push further than that, like all those athletes who never imagined they would have their heal down on the starting line, and then light it, yes, ignite it, yes, like feel it instead of walking around it like you normally do, okay, and shout it down if that&amp;rsquo;s what it takes even though you&amp;rsquo;ve never liked the taste of loud words, and then burn it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s the black and white I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Brief flash, bright light, everything illuminated, seeing for miles, but really just mere feet, walk around, you might wonder, guess at, chance at, did you stand up just when the fire went out? Yup, and now you&amp;rsquo;re stuck, in between the lie and the marble surface of that mind you just extinguished. Wow, not bad for one night, not bad at all, now travel close inside, yes, now, and bathe in it, bathe in all the self-doubt storybooks they read to you as children, every good versus fair, and imagine good like a little nub of a crayon with legs and arms, retired now because he&amp;rsquo;s been drawing all his life, and he&amp;rsquo;s waving at you, smiling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>